certapet.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy | CertaPet

**THIS NOTICE DESCRIBES HOW MEDICAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAY BE USED AND DISCLOSED AND HOW YOU CAN GET ACCESS TO THIS INFORMATION. PLEASE REVIEW IT CAREFULLY.**  
This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Cloud Clinic LLC, the owner of this website ([CertaPet.com](https://www.certapet.com/)). Cloud Clinic LLC is required to abide by the terms of the current Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify our privacy practices, which may apply to existing and subsequently collected health information. A copy of the current notice is posted at CertaPet.com. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy on this website. Applicable law requires Cloud Clinic LLC to maintain the privacy of your protected health information and to provide you with notice of our legal duties and privacy practices with respect to protected health information.  
Your authorization of these practices is essential for us to provide our services. We need you to provide accurate information so that we can conduct a preliminary screening to determine whether to connect you with one of the doctors or psychiatrists that we work with, who will assess whether to make a written recommendation for an emotional support animal. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, we will be unable to conduct our screening and you will not be contacted regarding a written recommendation. You can also request that we not use any information you submitted by clicking _[here.](https://www.certapet.com/contact/)_  
The only personal information we collect is your name, email address, responses to the preliminary questionnaire on the CertaPets.com website, and payment information.  
We use the information we collect to determine whether to connect you with a doctor or psychiatrist, who will assess whether to make a written recommendation for an emotional support animal. We obtain your written authorization to permit us to use your personal health information this way. Any other uses and disclosures not described in this notice will be made only with your written authorization, which you may subsequently revoke. We also use personal information to obtain payment from you.  
We use your name and email address to send you advertisements.  
When you pay for anything on our site using a credit or debit card, we collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information includes your name, account number, and other information necessary to process your payment, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you use to submit payment. We use an unaffiliated, payment processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.  
We automatically collect certain information from visitors to the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. Our website does not respond to your browser’s “do not track” signals or other mechanisms for indicating your preference regarding the collection personally identifiable information.  
Our website uses Google Analytics to collect information about how our site is used. This information includes how often someone visits our site, the pages viewed, and prior sites visited. We use this to improve our site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google Analytics puts a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser. You can also install Google’s Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.  
Our website also uses various advertising services (also called remarketing or retargeting services) provided by Google, Facebook, Twitter, AdRoll, and Infusionsoft (collectively, our “Advertising Service Providers”). They all work in a similar manner. When you view certain pages on our site, code on that page enables our Advertising Service Providers to place a cookie on your browser. These cookies collect and use anonymized identifiers, your IP address, and your website activity for advertising purposes. You will notice these services in operation after you leave our website, when advertisements from us appear on other websites. A complete description of the information that is collected and used, as well as instructions on how to opt-out, are available at: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). <https://www.facebook.com/help/1415256572060999>, <https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405%20>, <https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy>, and <http://www.infusionsoft.com/legal/privacy-policy>.  
We do not permit any other third parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our website.  
We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Additionally, we share and transfer your personal information only in the ways set forth in this privacy policy.  
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.  
This website is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.  
Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.  
This website is owned and operated by:  
Cloud Clinic LLC  
CertaPet  
3027 Marina Bay Dr. Suite 205  
League City, TX 77573  
Phone: (877) 207-0561  
Privacy@CertaPet.com  
Effective date: June 01, 2015

All product and Company names are Trademarks™ or Registered® trademarks of their respective holders.
